Okay, so we loop through the phrases in asap_list. Again, up here.
حسنًا، سنتصفح العبارات في asap_list. مرة أخرى، هنا.
And we want to assert that each phrase is not
ونرغب في التأكيد على أن كل عبارة ليست
in the start date column of our supposedly clean data frame.
في عمود تاريخ البدء لإطار البيانات النظيفة المفترض.
So assert phrase not in df_clean.StartDate and then there's some Pandas trickery here.
حسنًا، تأكدوّا من أن العبارة ليست في df_clean.StartDate، وتوجد بعض الخدع في Pandas هنا.
We actually need to type in. values here.
سنحتاج حقًا إلى كتابة in.values هنا.
If not, as I'll show you below,
إذا لم يكن الأمر كذلك، كما سنوضح لكم أدناه،
Pandas check to see if each phrase is in the index column of df_clean.StartDate.
فتتأكد Pandas من معرفة ما إذا كانت كل عبارة موجودة في عمود فهرس df_clean.StartDate.
We want the values,
نريد القيم،
and if we process the cell and we have no assertion errors, we're good.
وإذا قمنا بمعالجة الخلية وليس لدينا أي أخطاء في التأكيد، فنحن جيدون.
Our cleaning code worked. And great.
كود التنظيف يعمل. هذا رائع.
So this is what would happen if there was a phrase left.
حسنًا، هذا ما سيحدث لو ظلت عبارة ما.
There should be plenty of entries with ASAP.
يجب أن يكون هناك الكثير من الإدخالات بها ASAP.
6,856, in fact.
6856، في الواقع.
So if we assert that ASAP is not in df_clean.StartDate.values,
إذا تأكدنا أن ASAP لا توجد في df_clean.StartDate.values،
Python should yell at us and it does. AssertionError.
يجب أن ينبهنا Python ويفعل ذلك. AssertionError.